GEORGE ALKHOULI

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have experience in designing and developing front-end for websites, in addition to experience in graphic design, designs for social media sites and personal cards, managing social media pages and digital marketing, in addition to experience in technical support like solving problems, providing solutions and connecting devices. within one network.

WORK HISTORY

.Graphic Design, 02\2022- 03\2023 Freelancer,Lattakia,Syria (PhotoSop, illustrator)

.FrontEnd Web Developer, 01\2022-03\2023 Freelancer,Lattakia,Syria (Html, CSS,Sass, Botstrap JavaScript, React)

.IT Engineer, 02\2019- 01\2022 Lamir Hotel&Resort, Lattakia, Syria Experience in technical

support and the ability to solve problems related to the existing local network, in

05\2018- 10\2021

.Programming and Repairing Mobile (Having simple experience in solving software problems for devices and creating applications with simple interfaces).

01\2022- 09\2022

• Computer hardware and software Maintenance (Perform comprehensive computers maintenance and solve existing problems). Address: United Arab Emirates/Dubai

Phone: +971 502265223

Email: georgealkhouli1@gmail.com

Date of brith: 1,Jan,2000

SKILLS

- .PhotoShop
- .illustrator
- .HTML
- .CSS
- .Bootstrap
- .SASS
- .JavaScript
- .CCNA
- .MCSA
- .N+
- A+

.MicrosoftOffice(Excel,Word,
PowerPoint)

Additional Skills:

.Customer Service Skills-Expert

- .Work Under Pressure-Expert
- .Teamwork-Expert
- .Proessional and Responsible-Expert

EDUCATION

Graduation (71%) Applied Engineering, Tishreen University Specialized in maintenance, programming and networking

Languages

Arabic- Native

English- (3B) Advaced